throneit.com 2011-12-24

# ThroneIt - 'Just Throne It!' - Privacy Policy

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [[click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/]](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or Play our hosted DotA games. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.. 

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature To send periodic emails The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and . 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.throneit.com/terms. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 7-13-2009 

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. http://www.throneit.com contact@throneit.com Privacy Policy Created by Free Privacy Policy  |   

| 

[DotA Ladder](http://www.throneit.com/dota/ladder/) \- [DotA Safelist](http://www.throneit.com/dota/safelist/) \- [Forums](http://forums.throneit.com/) \- [Contact](http://www.throneit.com/contact) \- [Donate](http://www.throneit.com/donate) \- [Privacy Policy](http://www.throneit.com/privacypolicy)   
copyright © 2009 ThroneIt.com   
Supplying North America, South America, Europe, Asia, Australia, and the rest of the world with DotA Stats, DotA Ranks, DotA Stat Tracking, Top Tier DotA Players, DotA Ladders, DotA Elo Scores, DotA public games, DotA competitive games, DotA Hosting, DotA Communities, Defense of the Ancients enjoyment for all, and StarCraft 2 (SC2) Melee & Custom Maps.
